<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSETech</string>
    <string name="c1">Android Development:</string>
    <string name="c2">Artificial Intelligence</string>
    <string name="c3">Cybersecurity</string>
    <string name="c4">Data Science</string>
    <string name="c5">DevOps</string>
    <string name="c6">Game Development</string>
    <string name="c7">Machine Learning</string>
    <string name="c8">UI &amp; UX Design</string>
    <string name="c9">Full Stack Web Development</string>
    <string name="c10">Web3</string>
    <string name="d1">App development refers to crafting software for diverse devices, involving planning, coding, testing, and deployment to meet specific needs.It encompasses ideation, design, development, and iteration for optimal functionality and user experience.</string>
    <string name="l1">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/App%20Development</string>
    <string name="d2">Artificial Intelligence (AI) is the field focused on creating systems capable of performing tasks that typically require human intelligence, such as visual perception, speech recognition, decision-making, and language translation </string>
    <string name="l2">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Artificial%20Intelligence</string>
    <string name="d3">Cybersecurity involves the practice of protecting systems, networks, and data from digital attacks, unauthorized access, and damage. It includes measures and protocols designed to safeguard information integrity, confidentiality, and availability. Cybersecurity encompasses risk assessment, threat detection, incident response, and continuous monitoring to ensure robust defense against evolving cyber threats.</string>
    <string name="l3">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Cybersecurity</string>
    <string name="d4">Data science is the field that utilizes scientific methods, algorithms, and systems to extract insights and knowledge from structured and unstructured data.</string>
    <string name="l4">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Data%20Science</string>
    <string name="d5">DevOps is a combination of software development (Dev) and operations (Ops). It is defined as a software engineering methodology which aims to integrate the work of development teams and operations teams by facilitating a culture of collaboration and shared responsibility. The DevOps methodology aims to shorten the systems development lifecycle and provide continuous delivery with high software quality.</string>
    <string name="l5"> https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/DevOps</string>
    <string name="d6">Game development involves the creation of video games, encompassing everything from concept design to coding, art creation, and testing. It requires knowledge of various programming languages, game engines, and design principles. </string>
    <string name="l6"> https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Game%20Development</string>
    <string name="d7">Machine Learning is a type of technology that allows computers to learn and make decisions on their own by analyzing patterns in data. It’s like teaching a computer to recognize things, predict outcomes, and improve its performance over time without being explicitly programmed for each task </string>
    <string name="l7">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Machine%20learning</string>
    <string name="d8">UI (User Interface) Design is about making the visual parts of a website or app look good and be easy to use. UX (User Experience) Design focuses on ensuring that users have a smooth, enjoyable experience when interacting with a website or app, making sure it’s intuitive and meets their needs. </string>
    <string name="l8">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/UI-UX%20Design </string>
    <string name="d9">Web Development involves creating and maintaining websites. It includes everything from coding the structure and layout (frontend) to managing the server and database (backend), ensuring that websites are functional, fast, and user-friendly.</string>
    <string name="l9"> https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Web%20Development/Full%20stack%20Development</string>
    <string name="d10"> Web3 is the next-generation internet characterized by decentralization, blockchain technology, and user empowerment. It replaces central authorities with peer-to-peer interactions, relies on blockchain for trustless transactions, and emphasizes data ownership and privacy. Web3 features decentralized applications, smart contracts, and cryptocurrencies, fostering a more open, collaborative, and user-centric online ecosystem.</string>
    <string name="l10">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Web3 </string>
    <string name="c11">Computer Architecture</string>
    <string name="l11">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Computer%20Architecture</string>
    <string name="d11">Computer Architecture is the study of the structure, organization, and design of computer systems. This curated collection offers valuable Computer Architecture resources contributed by talented individuals.</string>
    <string name="c12">Computer Networks</string>
    <string name="l12">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Computer%20Networks</string>
    <string name="d12">A computer network is a collection of interconnected devices that can communicate with each other and share resources. These devices, known as nodes, can include computers, servers, networking hardware, and other peripherals. The purpose of a computer network is to enable devices to exchange data and resources efficiently and securely.</string>
    <string name="c13">Operating System</string>
    <string name="l13">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Operating%20System%20(OS)</string>
    <string name="d13">An operating system (OS) serves as the intermediary between computer hardware and software applications, facilitating efficient resource management and providing essential services for program execution. Understanding the intricacies of operating systems is vital for maximizing system performance and ensuring seamless user experiences.</string>
    <string name="c14">Linux Development</string>
    <string name="l14">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Linux%20Development</string>
    <string name="d14">Linux development refers to creating software for the Linux operating system, encompassing everything from kernel programming to application development. It involves understanding Linux internals, using development tools, and following best practices to build robust and efficient software.</string>
    <string name="c15">Data Structures and Algorithm (DSA)</string>
    <string name="l15">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Data%20Structures%20and%20Algorithm%20(DSA)</string>
    <string name="d15">Data Structures and Algorithms (DSA) refer to the study of methods for organizing and storing data and the design of procedures (algorithms) for solving problems, which operate on these data structures.</string>
    <string name="c16">MongoDB</string>
    <string name="l16">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/DBMS%20(Database)/MongoDB</string>
    <string name="d16">MongoDB is a NoSQL, document-oriented database designed to store and retrieve large amounts of data quickly and efficiently.</string>
    <string name="c17">MySQL</string>
    <string name="l17">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/DBMS%20(Database)/MySQL</string>
    <string name="d17">MySQL is an open-source relational database management system (RDBMS). Its name is a combination of "My", the name of co-founder Michael Widenius\'s daughter My, and "SQL", the acronym for Structured Query Language. A relational database organizes data into one or more data tables in which data may be related to each other; these relations help structure the data.</string>
    <string name="c18">NoSQL</string>
    <string name="l18">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/DBMS%20(Database)/NoSQL</string>
    <string name="d18">NoSQL is a type of database management system (DBMS) that is designed to handle and store large volumes of unstructured and semi-structured data. Unlike traditional relational databases that use tables with pre-defined schemas to store data, NoSQL databases use flexible data models that can adapt to changes in data structures and are capable of scaling horizontally to handle growing amounts of data.</string>
    <string name="c19">FrontEnd Web Development</string>
    <string name="l19">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Web%20Development/Frontend%20Development</string>
    <string name="d19">Frontend development involves creating the visual and interactive aspects of a website or application that users directly engage with. It combines HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build responsive and user-friendly interfaces. Frontend developers focus on enhancing user experience by ensuring design consistency, performance optimization, and seamless interaction across different devices and browsers</string>
    <string name="c20">Backend Development</string>
    <string name="l20">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Web%20Development/Backend%20Development</string>
    <string name="d20">Backend development refers to the server-side part of web development, where the primary focus is on how a website or web application works. This involves everything that users do not see directly when they interact with a web application. Backend developers are responsible for creating and maintaining the technology that powers the components enabling the user-facing side of websites to exist. This typically includes databases, server logic, APIs, and server configuration. Essentially, the backend serves as the backbone of a website, managing data, user connections, and the performance of the system.</string>
    <string name="c21">Kotlin</string>
    <string name="l21">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Programming%20Languages/Kotlin</string>
    <string name="d21">Kotlin is a modern, statically-typed programming language developed by JetBrains. It is designed to be fully interoperable with Java, making it an excellent choice for Android development, server-side applications, and much more. Kotlin combines object-oriented and functional programming features, and its concise syntax helps developers write clear and expressive code.</string>
    <string name="c22">C++</string>
    <string name="l22">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Programming%20Languages/C%2B%2B</string>
    <string name="d22">C++ is a powerful general-purpose programming language that supports procedural, object-oriented, and generic programming paradigms. Known for its performance and efficiency, C++ is widely used in software development, game development, system/software applications, and real-time simulations.</string>
    <string name="c23">C Programming</string>
    <string name="l23">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Programming%20Languages/C</string>
    <string name="d23">C is a powerful and widely-used procedural programming language. Known for its efficiency and versatility, C is commonly used in system programming, embedded systems, and low-level programming.</string>
    <string name="c24">Java</string>
    <string name="l24">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Programming%20Languages/Java</string>
    <string name="d24">Java is a high-level, class-based, object-oriented programming language which is one of the most widely used and versatile programming languages in the world. Known for its portability across platforms, robustness, and rich API, Java is used in a variety of applications ranging from web development, mobile apps, enterprise solutions, and large-scale systems.</string>
    <string name="c25">Python</string>
    <string name="l25">https://github.com/jfmartinz/ResourceHub/tree/main/Programming%20Languages/Python</string>
    <string name="d25">Python supports multiple programming paradigms, including procedural, object-oriented, and functional programming, and has a large, supportive community, contributing to a vast ecosystem of tools and resources.</string>
</resources>